So, Diane and Carrie, to start out, what exactly is A/B testing?
Diane、Carrie 究竟什么是 A/B 测试？
>> So, A/B testing is a general methodology used online when
A/B 测试是一个用于在线测试的常规方法
you want to test out a new product or a feature.
可用来测试新产品或新功能
And what you're doing is you're going to take two sets of users and
你需要做的是设置两组用户
you're going to show one set, a control set, your existing product or
将其中一组设置为对照组 采用已有的产品或功能
a feature, and then another set, your experiment, the new version.
另一组是实验组 采用新版产品或功能
And what you're going to do is,
你需要做的是
you're going to say, how did these users respond differently,
找到上述用户做出的不同响应
in order to determine which version of your feature is better?
然后确认哪个版本的功能更好
>> So, should you use A/B testing for every change you're considering, or
对所有考虑进行的变更使用 A/B 测试 还是说
are there certain types of changes it works better for?
A/B 测试是否更适用于一些特定类型的改变？
>> So I was talking to John Lilly.
我曾经和 John Lilly 讨论过
He's a VC at Greylock now, but
他现在是 Greylock 的 VC 但是
he used to be the CEO of Mozilla, and he came up with a great analogy.
他曾任 Mozilla 的 CEO 他打了一个十分恰当的比方
And his analogy is that A/B testing is really useful for
他说 A/B 测试
helping you climb to the peak of your current mountain.
能够帮你爬上你面前高山的顶峰
But if you want figure out whether you want to be on this mountain or
但是如果你想弄清楚自己是否想爬上这座山还是另一座山
another mountain, A/B testing isn't so useful.
那么 A/B 测试就没那么有用了
>> Now that said, you can test a pretty wide variety of things with A/B testing,
也就是说 你可以通过 A/B 测试对很大范围的事情进行测试
everything from some new features, additions to your UI,
比如一些新功能 用户界面中增加的内容
different look for your website, and a lot of companies use it.
网站的不同外观 很多公司都在使用 A/B 测试
So for example, when Amazon first started doing personalized
例如 Amazon 首次开始做个性化推荐时
recommendations, they wanted to see whether people really bought more stuff.
他们想看一下人们是否真的会购买更多商品
And they discovered that actually had a signfiicant increase in
他们发现由于个性化推荐
revenue from the personalized recommendations.
他们的收益有了显著增加
So, you can use it for fairly complicated changes.
所以 你可以将它用于十分复杂的改变
Now, Google maybe took it a little too far sometimes, so
现在 Google 有时可能 A/B 测试做太多了
once we ran 41 different shades of blue in the UI to see how users responded,
有一次我们在用户界面中运行 41 个不同的蓝色阴影 来查看用户有什么反响
if they reacted.
如果他们做出反应
And on the one hand it was interesting and useful internally,
它本身十分有趣并有用
but it might have been going a little too far with those experiments.
但是实验做的太过了
>> Maybe, but we can also test less user visible changes.
但是我们能够测试少量的用户可见的变化
So, for example, ranking changes.
例如 排名变动
LinkedIn tested a change where they were trying to figure out whether they should
LinkedIn 测试了一个改变 尝试确定他们是否应显示新文章
show a news article or an encouragement to basically add new contacts.
还是鼓励大家增加新联系人
That's a ranking change.
这就是排名变动
Google does a lot of ranking, between our search lists and
Google 做了很多检索列表和广告之间的排名
our ads, we test all of those changes also via A/B testing.
我们也通过 A/B 测试对所有上述改变进行了测试
>> You can also test changes that you're not even sure a user would notice.
你也可以针对你不确信用户是否会注意到的改变进行测试
So for example, 100 milliseconds is not a lot of page load time, but,
例如 100 毫秒的页面加载时间不是太多 但是
both Amazon and Google have run experiments.
Amazon 和 Google 都运行了测试
Amazon showed in 2007 that, for every 100 milliseconds they added to the page,
Amazon 在 2007 年证实 每个页面增加 100 毫秒的延迟
they actually had a 1% decrease in revenue.
会导致收入降低 1%
And for Google, we have similar results, that you find,
对于 Google 来说 我们得到了相似的结果 你可以发现
even though 100 milliseconds doesn't seem like that much, on average,
平均来看 虽然 100 毫秒看起来不多
the number of queries people do actually decreases for
但每增加100 毫秒的延迟
every 100 milliseconds of latency that you add.
人们查询的数量真地降低了
>> Wow, so those are some things you can learn from A/B testing.
这就是可以从 A/B 测试中学到的东西
What are some things you can't do with A/B testing?
那你不能用 A/B 测试做的事情是哪些呢？
>> A/B testing isn't as useful testing out new experiences.
在测试新的体验时 A/B 测试的用途就没那么大了
And you can sort of think about this in the obvious way, right?
但是你可以用更明显的方式考虑这个问题 对吧？
You know, you're testing a new experience and you've got an existing
你在测试新的体验时 你当前已有的那些用户
set of users and they are like, hey, you just changed my experience,
可能会觉得 你改变了我的体验
what happened, I liked my old way and I'm kind of like grrr, right?
发生了什么 我喜欢我原来的方式 我有点不高兴 对吧？
That's called change aversion.
这也被称为改变厌恶症
The other thing is that they can be like, oh, well, this is new,
另一方面 他们可能觉得 这是新的
and they test out everything.
然后他们尝试所有东西
That's called a novelty effect, right?
这就被称为新奇效应 对吧？
And so what happens in a new experience is there are sort of like two issues.
那么 在新的体验中会发生什么 有点像两个问题
One is a question of, what is your baseline for comparison?
一个问题是 你比较的基准是什么
But two is a question about how much time you need
第二个问题 你需要多少时间
In order to actually have your users adapt to the new experience,
为了在实际中让你的用户接受新的体验
so that you can actually say what is going to be the plateaued experience so
实际上就是平稳的体验会是什么样
that I can actually make a robust decision.
我能够据此做出稳健的决策
>> Yeah, and time can be a problem for other reasons.
由于其他一些原因 时间也可能成为难题所在
So, for example, if you have a website that recommends apartment rentals.
例如 你有一个网站 推荐公寓租赁的
People don't look for apartments that often, and
人们寻找公寓不是那么频繁
what you really want is return business, or maybe you want to grow your business
那么 你真正想要的是回报的业务 或通过推荐给其他喜欢这项服务的人
by referrals to other people who like your service.
扩大业务
And the reality is, in the scope of an experiment it's going to be really hard
现实是 在试验的范围内
to measure whether people actually come back to you from more referrals.
十分难以测定 人们是否真的因为更多的推介回到你的网站
And even if they refer their friends,
即便人们向他们的朋友推荐
well, honestly is it going to be next week?
老实说 是否需要等到下一周？
Is it going to be six months from now?
是否需要等到六个月后？
So, there's certain things that you may want to know about your site,
所以你可能想知道关于你的网站的一些东西
that are pretty difficult to get at, through short term A/B testing, and
但通过短期的 A/B 测试却十分难以实现
we'll talk in lesson three about some options for
我们将在第三课中讨论
coming up with some metrics that are good proxies for that kind of thing.
针对这些情况 有哪些好的指标可以选择
>> So the last example that we'll give for when A/B testing isn't as useful,
因此 最后我们提供的示例中 A/B 测试不是十分有效
is that A/B testing can't really tell you if you're missing something.
因为 A/B 测试无法真实地告诉你是否遗漏了什么东西
So, let's say you're on a digital camera review site.
现在 假设你在做数码相机评论网站
A/B testing can tell you whether or
A/B 测试可以告诉你是否需要
not you should be showing this camera review above this camera review, but
在这相机评论上面发表相机评论
A/B testing can't really tell you if you're missing this entire other camera
但是 A/B 测试无法告诉你 你是否完全忽略了
that you should be reviewing but you aren't reviewing at all.
其他需要你来评价但是你根本没有评价的相机
>> Got it.
明白了